♪ IT SEEMS TODAY
THAT ALL YOU SEE ♪
♪ IS VIOLENCE IN MOVIES
AND SEX ON T.V. ♪
♪ BUT WHERE ARE THOSE GOOD.
OLD-FASHIONED VALUES ♪
♪ ON WHICH WE USED TO RELY? ♪
♪ LUCKY THERE'S A FAMILY GUY ♪
♪ LUCKY THERE'S A MAN WHO'LL
POSITIVELY TELL YOU ♪
♪ ALL THE THINGS
THAT MAKE US ♪
♪ LAUGH 'N' CRY ♪
♪ HE'S A FAMILY GUY ♪
I'M... I'M IN
A RUT.
NOTHING THRILLS
ME ANYMORE.
I MEAN I... I
CAN'T EVEN THINK
OF A REASON
TO GET OFF THE BED
IN THE MORNING.
REALLY?
YOU WANT TO KNOW HOW
PATHETIC MY LIFE IS?
I'VE SEEN THAT
BEHIND THE MUSIC
WITH LEIF GARRETT
18 TIMES.
HEY. UH. HEY. LEIF.
IT'S BEEN A WHILE.
TOO LONG. MAN.
I'M SO SORRY ABOUT
EVERYTHING. MAN. I'M SO...
YOU READY FOR
A BOMBSHELL?
YOU SAVED MY LIFE
THAT NIGHT.
BUT... BUT I WAS
DRIVING. I...
I WAS ON A ROAD TO
DESTRUCTION. MAN.
THE ACCIDENT MAY
HAVE CRIPPLED ME.
BUT I'M ALIVE.
AREN'T I?
C-CAN WE TURN OFF
THE CAMERAS. DUDE?
IT'S... IT'S
LIKE I'M.
I DON'T KNOW.
TRAPPED IN
MY OWN LIFE.
WELL. BRIAN. YOU MAY BE
TOO INWARDLY FOCUSED.
TRY THINKING ABOUT THE NEEDS
OF OTHERS FOR A CHANGE.
WHY DON'T YOU DO
SOME VOLUNTEER WORK?
OH. THAT MAKES SENSE.
VOLUNTEER WORK.
THANKS. BRUCE.
YOU STILL HAVE
13 MORE MINUTES.
OH. DO I?
HMM.
I. UH. I NOTICE
YOU GOT A NEW
RECEPTIONIST.
HEH. NICE LITTLE
BODY ON HER. HUH?
THAT'S MY DAUGHTER.
WELL. WE COULD
PROBABLY CALL THIS
AN EARLY DAY. HUH?
ATTENTION. EVERYONE.
DUE TO SEVERAL
COMPLAINTS AND 2 DEATHS
RELATED TO WORKER FATIGUE.
I HAVE DECIDED TO THROW A
COMPANY PICNIC THIS SATURDAY.
HEY. DEREK. HOW ARE YOU
GETTING TO THE PICNIC?
I DON'T KNOW. I
DON'T HAVE A RIDE.
HEY. JOHN. YOU
GOT A 2-SEATER.
DON'T YOU?
HEY. DEREK.
M-MAYBE YOU GO
WITH JOHN. HUH? HUH?
FOR THE LAST TIME.
I'M NOT GAY!
THANKS ANYWAY. PETER.
HEY. WE'LL GET HIM.
HERE. RIGHT...
RIGHT THIS WAY.
WATCH YOUR STEP.
OK. THEY'RE
IN THE WOODS.
THE CAMERA
KEEPS ON MOVING.
UH. I THINK THEY'RE
LOOKING FOR SOME
WITCH OR SOMETHING.
I DON'T KNOW.
I WASN'T LISTENING.
NOTHING'S
HAPPENING.
SOMETHING
ABOUT A MAP.
NOTHING'S
HAPPENING.
IT'S OVER.
A LOT OF PEOPLE
IN THE AUDIENCE
LOOK PISSED.
NOW. REMEMBER.
CHRIS.
WE HAVE TO
WORK TOGETHER.
SO THAT
OUR STEPS...
OH. THIS IS MY
FAVORITE EVENT.
"CATCH THE GREASED
UP DEAF GUY."
GO!
YOU'RE NEVER
GONNA CATCH ME!
YOU'RE
WASTING
YOUR TIME!
FORGET ABOUT IT!
GO DO SOMETHING ELSE!
SEE YOU ALL
NEXT YEAR!
KING ME.
I DON'T WANT
TO PLAY ANYMORE.
THE PAIN.
I CAN'T LIVE
LIKE THIS. BRIAN.
I NEED YOU TO
PULL THE PLUG.
WH... I... I CAN'T.
BE MY ANGEL
AND SET ME FREE.
PLEASE?
OH. MY GOD!
YOU WERE REALLY
GONNA DO IT!
I... BUT... YOU...
NURSE. THIS DOG
IS TRYING TO
KILL ME! NURSE!
YOU ARE TWISTED. LADY!
Y-YOU HEAR ME?
YOU ARE SCREWED
UP IN THE HEAD!
THE WINNER OF
OUR FINAL CONTEST
WILL RECEIVE A
VERY SPECIAL PRIZE.
A WEEK'S
PAID VACATION!
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
OH. GOD. PLEASE.
LET IT BE FARTING.
PLEASE LET IT
BE A FART CONTEST.
THESE ARE
TRANQUILIZER DARTS.
I HAVE ENOUGH HERE TO
TAKE DOWN ROBERT DOWNEY JR.
ROBERT DOWNEY.
YES. WELL.
THE LAST ONE LEFT
STANDING WINS.
LET THE GAME BEGIN!
ALL RIGHT. DAD!
GO. PETER!
LOOK AT HIM!
HE RUNS LIKE
A WELSHMAN.
DOESN'T HE?
DOESN'T HE RUN
LIKE A WELSHMAN?
HEY THERE.
BRIAN.
HI. JOE.
HEY. BONNIE MAKING
CHICKEN MARSALA
TONIGHT?
NO. SHE MADE
THAT 3 NIGHTS AGO.
WOW. THAT'S
SOME NOSE YOU GOT!
YEAH. ONE TIME
IT ALMOST GOT ME
A SPOKESMAN DEAL.
"FOLLOW YOUR NOSE."
OH. I... I'M SORRY.
NO. TH-THAT WAS GOOD.
I JUST. I... I DIDN'T
THINK YOU WERE GONNA
GO SO CARTOONY
WITH IT.
WELL. HOW... HOW
WOULD YOU READ IT?
OH. I DON'T KNOW.
I WAS THINKING
OF DOING IT.
YOU KNOW.
GOOD. LIKE... LIKE
AN ACTOR.
BUT. YOU KNOW.
Y-YOUR WAY'S
GOOD. TOO.
YOU KNOW. WE COULD
USE A NOSE LIKE THAT
DOWN AT THE PRECINCT.
REALLY?
I GUESS IT'S JUST
DOWN TO YOU
AND ME. PETER.
ONE OF US IS GONNA
WIN THAT PAID VACATION.
I DON'T WANT TO
FEED GRANDMA BACON
WHILE SHE'S
IN THE BATHTUB.
PETER. ARE
YOU OK?
MR. WEED. I THINK
PETER NEEDS
A DOC... OOH.
WE HAVE
A WINNER!
HERE. KITTY. KITTY.
KITTY. KITTY.
NO DRUGS.
SHE'S GOOD.
HE'S CLEAN.
IT LOOKS LIKE
THAT'S IT. EXCEPT FOR
THE FLIGHT CREW.
HEY. HEY. BRIAN.
WHAT'S WITH THE
JOHNNY LAW ROUTINE?
SAY HELLO TO
OUR NEWEST NARC.
HE'S A NATURAL.
OH. YEAH?
HOW GOOD ARE YOU?
YOU'RE BACK
FROM MANILA.
YOU HAD LUMPIA
FOR DINNER.
THEN YOU MADE LOVE
TO 2 FILIPINO WOMEN
AND A MAN.
YOU MEAN 3
FILIPINO WOMEN!
NO!
WAIT A SECOND.
GOT SOMETHING.
THIS COULD BE
THE REAL DEAL. BOYS!
LET'S DO IT!
DON'T MOVE.
DIRT BAG!
AH. IT'S COKE! YES!
ALL RIGHT.
WE'VE GOT HIM!
THIS IS GREAT.
THIS IS THE RUSH
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR.
GOOD WORK. BRIAN.
UH. YOU STILL GOT
A LITTLE. UH...
OH. OH. THANKS.
SO. PETER. WHERE
SHALL WE GO FOR
YOUR WEEK OFF?
WELL. I WAS THINKING WE
COULD ALL GO TO PURGATORY.
LIKE WE DID LAST YEAR.
THIS ISN'T BAD.
IT'S NOT
THAT GOOD.
BUT IT'S NOT
THAT BAD.
IT'S SO-SO.
UH. MORE
OR LESS.
HEY. HEY. BRIAN.
IF COPS ARE PIGS.
DOES THAT MAKE
YOU A SNAUSAGE?
CLEVER. PETER.
DID YOU STAY UP ALL
NIGHT WRITING THAT?
I GOT TO BED
AROUND 2:00. 2:30.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT JOE SAID
THE STREET VALUE OF THAT
COCAINE WOULD'VE BEEN?
LET'S SEE.
4 AND A HALF KILOS
UNCUT NICARAGUAN.
UH. $1.7 MILL.
THAT AREA?
UH. YEAH.
THAT'S... THAT'S...
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU GUYS!
BRIAN'S FAMOUS!
YOU'RE A HERO!
WAY TO GO. PAL!
OH. COME ON.
STOP IT YOU GUYS.
IT'S NOTHING.
REALLY.
OH. LOIS. YOUR
TOAST IS READY.
WOW.
OH. MY.
MEG'S USING A
NEW CONDITIONER.
HE'S RIGHT!
HOW DO YOU LIKE THAT?
THAT'S AMAZING.
AND IT'S TIME
TO CHANGE STEWIE.
THAT'S PREPOSTEROUS.
I HAVEN'T... OH. THERE IT IS.
ALL RIGHT.
STOP THE CAR!
OVER THERE.
EVERYBODY FREEZE!
THIS IS A BUST!
BRIAN. THIS IS A
SUNDAY SCHOOL CLASS.
THE HELL IT IS!
PURE BOGOTA BULLION.
THIS IS A DRUG RING.
BUT THESE ARE JUST KIDS.
OH. YEAH?
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
RICKY.
THEY'RE NOT KIDS.
THEY'RE MIDGETS!
FILTHY.
DRUG-PEDDLING
MIDGETS!
OH. MY GOD!
LOOK OUT.
BRIAN!
UGH.
OH.
UH.
OOH.
AH.
NICE WORK.
ROOKIE.
YOU'RE A
CREDIT TO
THE FORCE.
ADDITIONAL GENERIC
COP COMPLIMENT. BRIAN.
THANKS. BUT
THE REAL HERO
HERE IS GOD
FOR BLESSING ME
WITH THIS NOSE
AND A FEW OTHER
EQUALLY AMAZING
APPENDAGES.
HUH?
OH!
WELL. I BETTER TAKE
THIS COCAINE DOWN
TO EVIDENCE.
OH. HEY. I'LL...
I'LL DO THAT.
UH. I'LL CATCH UP
WITH YOU GUYS
AT THE PUB.
SO IT'S
SETTLED.
WE'RE TAKING
A CRUISE TO
THE BAHAMAS!
AH. THIS IS GONNA BE GREAT.
CRUISES ARE THE BEST.
AND LOOK. IT SAYS
WE HAVE OUR CHOICE
OF CABINS.
PORT OR STARBOARD.
HO. LISTEN TO ME.
I SOUND LIKE
AN OLD SALT.
YES. THOUGH I MUST
SAY. I'VE ALWAYS
DREAMED OF A LIFE AT SEA.
♪
♪ I'M THE GREATEST CAPTAIN
OF THE QUEEN'S NAVY ♪
♪ AND YOUR RECORD
WILL STAND AS PROOF ♪
♪ BE IT GALLEY OR A FREIGHTER.
I'M AN EXPERT NAVIGATOR ♪
♪ AND YOU'RE ALSO
A WORLD-CLASS POOF ♪
♪ MY MANNER. QUITE EFFETE.
IS MISTAKEN ON THE STREET ♪
♪ FOR A SAILOR WHO
CAN PIROUETTE ON CUE ♪
♪ WELL. DESPITE
YOUR POINT OF VIEW ♪
♪ I CAN THRILL A GIRL OR 2 ♪
♪ BUT I'D RATHER
GET IT ON WITH YOU ♪
SORRY TO BE TARDY
TO THE PARTY.
WOW. BRIAN.
HAVE YOU
LOST WEIGHT?
YOU GOTTA TELL ME
YOUR SECRET.
HERE'S A HINT.
PUT DOWN THE FORK! FACE!
SO HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
MY DAY?
UN-FREAKIN'-BELIEVABLE!
FIRST WE NAILED
THIS BASTARD WHO
HAD THE GALL
TO HIDE HIS STUFF
IN HIS DAUGHTER'S DOLL!
HER DOLL.
FOR GOD'S SAKE!
OH. WHERE'S THE LINE ANYMORE?
WELL. I GOT NEWS FOR YOU.
IT'S... IT'S NOT EVEN ON
THE RADAR SCREEN!
THE DAYS OF
DECENCY AND VIRTUE
ARE GONE. HONEY! BAM!
FREAKIN' EVAPORATED.
LIKE A DINGY.
STINKIN' MUD PUDDLE.
ONE... ONE DAY YOU... YOU
SEE YOUR REFLECTION IN IT.
AND THE NEXT DAY.
IT'S A... IT'S A DAMN OIL SPOT
ON YOUR CRACKED DRIVEWAY.
STARING BACK AT YOU.
MOCKING YOU.
BLAH. BLAH. BLAH!
KNOWING THE PERVERTED
TRUTH THAT ROTS IN THE
PIT OF YOUR SOUL.
THAT'S HOW MY
FREAKIN' DAY WAS.
YOU KNOW WHAT
I HAVEN'T HAD
IN A WHILE?
BIG LEAGUE CHEW.
SO TAKE IT FROM
ME. MCGRIFFIN.
THE DRUG DOG.
IF YOU REALLY
WANT TO GET HIGH.
IT'S AS EASY AS
BEING YOURSELF.
WELL. KIDS.
I'M GONNA PASS
THINGS OFF NOW TO...
GERALD. THE
HAPPY AND ABSTINENT
POLICE CLOWN.
HEY. KIDS!
DO YOU KNOW
WHY I'M HAPPY?
BECAUSE I'M
FREE OF "S"...
"T"...
"D" s!
THAT MCGRIFFIN
GUY WAS SO COOL!
TOTALLY! I'M
NEVER DOING
DRUGS NOW!
AHH!
GOT MILK?
CHRIS. BEFORE YOU
GO ON A CRUISE.
YOU GOTTA BUILD
UP A BASE TAN.
BUT. DAD. I HEARD
THAT IF YOU USE
TANNING BEDS.
YOU CAN GET
SOMETHING CALLED
"MELANOMA."
AW. THAT'S JUST FANCY
TALK FOR "SEXIFIED."
NOW CLIMB IN.
HEY. WHAT KIND OF
TANNING BOOTH
IS THIS?
CAN'T YOU READ?
THOSE AREN'T
TANNING BOOTHS.
THAT WHOLE ROW
IS TIME MACHINES!
AW. CRAP! WHERE
THE HELL IS HE?
HEY. DAD. I'M IN
THE BIBLE DAYS.
AND THERE'S A WHOLE STADIUM
OF PEOPLE CLAPPING FOR ME.
OH. LOOK.
MY VERY OWN LION!
OH. MY GOD!
HUH.
MUST'VE GOT
THE WRONG HAT.
AND NOW. HERE'S
SOMETHING WE HOPE
YOU'LL REALLY LIKE.
WHOA. BRIAN.
THERE'S NO SMOKING
IN THE TERMINAL.
HEY. HEY. THERE'S
WORSE THINGS THAN
NICOTINE. PAL!
AND I'M GONNA
FIND 'EM.
PATIENCE.
LAD.
IT TOOK DEAR
ST. PATRICK
MORE THAN A DAY
TO CLEAR THE
EMERALD ISLE
OF SNAKES.
CAN THE IRISH
CRAP. WILL YOU.
HOROWICZ?
OK.
OPEN IT!
AHH! LET ME
GO! HELP!
HELP!
ALL RIGHT. WHERE'S
THE STASH?
I'LL DO A FREAKIN'
BODY-CAVITY SEARCH.
I SWEAR!
AHH!
SIR.
WE APOLOGIZE.
GRIFFIN. THERE'S
NO EASY WAY
TO SAY THIS.
I THINK YOU HAVE
A DRUG PROBLEM.
A DRUG PROBLEM?
WHAT'S THIS
REALLY ABOUT?
JEALOUSY?
AM I STEALING
YOUR THUNDER. JOE.
IS THAT IT?
GIVE ME YOUR BADGE.
FINE!
BY THE WAY.
HOROWICZ.
YOU SHOULD
SHOW JOE YOUR
IMPRESSION OF HIM.
OH. W-WELL. I. UH...
IT'S NOT AS GOOD
AS. YOU KNOW.
MY IRISH COP.
IT'S JUST A
LITTLE THING I...
"LOOK AT ME!
I'M JOE!
"MY LEGS DON'T WORK
BUT I MAKE UP FOR IT
"BY HAVING A VERY
STRONG UPPER BODY!"
WELL. I DO
SAY THAT.
OH. THE OLD MAN
AND THE SEA.
I SEE YOU'RE
GETTING IN THE MOOD
FOR OUR CRUISE.
YEAH.
STUPID FISHERMAN.
SITTING OUT THERE IN A BOAT
YAMMERING TO HIMSELF.
HE DOESN'T EVEN
KNOW I'M WATCHING HIM.
AH. SPLENDID.
FIDO MCCOKE-FIEND IS HOME.
EVERYBODY.
THIS IS TINA.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOU?
HOW ABOUT A LITTLE
LESS QUESTIONS.
AND A LITTLE MORE
SHUT THE HELL UP?
YOU KNOW. JUST BECAUSE YOU
CAN'T FEEL YOUR TEETH.
DOESN'T MEAN THE GIRL
CAN'T FEEL YOUR INSULTS.
HELLO. I'M
LOIS GRIFFIN.
WELCOME TO
OUR HOME.
SO. WHAT?
SHE'S LIKE YOUR MOM
OR SOMETHING?
TINA. CAN I GET YOU
A WARM WASHCLOTH
TO WIPE THE DRIED BLOOD
FROM UNDER YOUR NOSE?
HERE. BABY. I'LL SHOW
YOU THE CHANNEL LOIS
DOESN'T KNOW ABOUT.
BRIAN. WOULD YOU...
CHRIS. LOOK AWAY!
MEG. TAKE
STEWIE UPSTAIRS!
WAIT! WAIT! THAT
MAN SEEMS TO
HAVE SUFFERED
A RATHER SERIOUS
SNAKEBITE!
BRIAN. WOULD YOU
PLEASE ASK
YOUR NEW FRIEND
TO LEAVE NOW?
OH. SORRY. THINGS
GETTING A LITTLE
TOO REAL
FOR THE STEPFORD
WIFE?
A-AND LOOK
AT YOU TWO.
QUASIMODO
AND LUMPY.
I... I LEAVE MORE
PERSONALITY
IN TIGHTLY COILED
PILES ON THE LAWN.
OH. DO ME!
DO ME NEXT!
COME ON. BABY GIRL.
LET'S GO TO THE PARK.
HEY. DOC.
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
YOUR FAMILY HAS
SOMETHING THEY'D
LIKE TO SAY TO YOU.
"BRIAN.
I KNOW I DON'T
SPEAK UP MUCH
"AND IT'S... IT'S
REALLY HARD FOR ME
"TO TALK ABOUT
MY FEELINGS. BUT..."
W-WHY DON'T WE START
WITH SOMEONE MORE
INTERESTING? PETER?
"BRIAN. EVER
SINCE YOUR ADDICTION.
YOU'VE BEEN A JERK.
"I MISS THE GOOD OLD DAYS
WHEN YOU WERE MY SIDEKICK."
UH. SO SHE
HATED MY TIE
UNTIL I TOLD HER
IT WAS MADE
OUT OF 100 PERCENT
BUTTAFUOCO FIBER.
YEAH.
UH. YEAH.
HEY. BRIAN. HOW ABOUT
A LITTLE TIE MUSIC?
♪ PETER'S TIE. PETER'S TIE ♪
♪ THAT'S BECAUSE
PETER'S THE GUY ♪
ALL RIGHT. THAT'S IT.
A LITTLE TIE MUSIC.
HE-HEE.
YEAH!
LOOK. YOU... YOU
GUYS GOT IT ALL WRONG.
I... I... I...
I'M SO SORRY. EVERYONE!
OH. GOD.
I NEED HELP!
WELL. I GUESS NOW WE KNOW
WHAT KIND OF DOG HE IS.
A MELAN-COLLIE.
NOTHING?
W-W-WAIT. NO.
I... I SHOULD'VE SAID...
I SHOULD'VE SAID
"CHI-WAH-WAH."
I DON'T HAVE
TO... IMPRESS YOU.
LOOK. I... I'M NOT
INSENSITIVE. LOIS.
BUT I JUST DON'T
SEE WHY WE GOTTA
CANCEL OUR CRUISE
JUST BECAUSE THE
DOG'S A COKEHEAD.
WE'RE NOT GOING ON VACATION
WHILE BRIAN'S IN REHAB.
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
WAIT TILL NEXT YEAR.
AW. MAN!
LOOK. I'LL MAKE IT UP
TO YOU. I HAVE A COUSIN
WHO WORKS AT CLUB MED.
♪ ME MIND ON FIRE ♪
♪ ME SOUL ON FIRE.
FEELING HOT. HOT. HOT ♪
HOLY CRAP!
LOOK AT THIS PLACE.
THIS IS WHERE
GOD WOULD COME
IF HE HAD TO
STOP DOING BLOW.
THEY HAVE
TENNIS COURTS!
AND A FULL SPA!
WOW! NO WONDER
PEOPLE DO DRUGS!
GOOD LUCK.
BRIAN.
I JUST KNOW
YOU'RE GONNA
GET CLEAN.
HECK. SHOULDN'T
BE TOO HARD
TO GET CLEAN
WITH ALL THESE
MINERAL BATHS
AND JACUZZIS.
OH. I SEE.
THE FAT MAN MAKES
A PUN. AND EVERYONE
WETS THEMSELVES.
I GIVE YOU GOLD.
AND I GET SQUAT.
I'LL BE IN THE CAR.
THAT WAS A VERY
PRODUCTIVE
FIRST DAY. BRIAN.
OUR GOAL HERE
IS TO FIND
YOUR X-FACTOR.
THE ELEMENT IN YOUR LIFE
THAT MADE YOU TURN TO DRUGS
IN THE FIRST PLACE..
WELL. JUST...
JUST HAVING
SOME TIME AWAY
TO SORT THINGS
OUT IS GONNA
DO WONDERS.
THANKS. DOCTOR.
WH... WHAT ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
I'M ON
VACATION!
OH. AND IF
ANYONE ASKS.
I'M ALSO ON SMACK.
PETER. THIS... THIS
IS A DETOX CLINIC.
YOU CAN'T
VACATION HERE.
WHY NOT?
THIS PLACE IS WAY
BETTER THAN A CRUISE.
Y-YOU SHOULD'VE
SEEN IT.
I WHIPPED A SPEED FREAK'S
ASS AT HORSESHOES TODAY.
PETER. THIS ISN'T
A VACATION FOR ME.
FOR GOD'S SAKE.
I'M TRYING
TO GET HEALTHY!
YEAH. OK. OK.
ALL RIGHT.
HEY. HEY. SOFTBALL
THIS AFTERNOON.
A BUNCH OF US ADDICTS
ARE TAKING ON
THE PREGNANT
TEENAGERS FROM
ACROSS THE LAKE.
OK. COME ON.
EVERYONE.
EXERCISE IS
AN IMPORTANT PART
OF RECOVERY.
JUST WORK WITH
THE RESISTANCE
OF THE WATER.
10 MORE
REPS.
OK. AND ONE.
AND 2. AND 3...
YEAH! I'M ALSO
ADDICTED TO BOOBIES!
I'LL TRADE
YOU THIS FOR
YOUR CUPCAKE.
WHAT? IT WAS
JUST CARPET FRESH.
I'M ON YOUR SIDE.
I'VE BEEN
OBSERVING
YOUR BEHAVIOR.
AND I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE AN ADDICT.
I THINK YOU'RE
AN IDIOT.
WELL. I DON'T
PAY YOU TO THINK.
HOT LIPS.
IN FACT. I DON'T
PAY YOU AT ALL.
COUNT IT!
I'LL BE KEEPING
MY EYE ON YOU.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
UH. M-MY NAME?
UH. UH...
"PEA"
UH. UH. UH...
"TEAR"
UH. UH...
"GRIFFIN."
YEAH. YEAH.
PETER GRIFFIN.
OH. CRAP.
HEY. BRIAN.
I WAS LOOKING
FOR YOU.
HEY. YOU WANT TO GO
MESS WITH THE PREGNANT
TEENS ACROSS THE LAKE?
I... I CAN'T. GROUP
THERAPY. 2:00.
OH. MAN. I PEEKED
IN ON ONE OF THOSE.
IT WAS MORE BORING
THAN WHEN I WAS
A SECURITY GUARD
FOR GEORGE HARRISON.
♪ CHARLES IN CHARGE ♪
♪ OF OUR DAYS
AND OUR NIGHTS ♪
♪ CHARLES IN CHARGE ♪
♪ OF OUR WRONGS
AND OUR RIGHTS ♪
♪ AND I SAY. I WANT
CHARLES IN CHARGE ♪
HEY! HEY! HEY!
QUIET DOWN.
UP THERE!
YOU WACKY BEATLE.
WELL. I... I HAVE BEEN
MAKING A LOT OF
PROGRESS LATELY.
I GUESS MISSING ONE
SESSION WOULDN'T BE
THE END OF THE WORLD.
THERE YOU GO!
HEY. WHAT DO YOU THINK
THEY PUT IN THE BUG JUICE?
BUGS.
NO. THEY DON'T!
COME ON!
SHUT UP!
WELL. I HOPE
YOU'RE PROUD
OF YOURSELVES.
14 PREMATURE BIRTHS!
SORRY. DOC. I...
I DON'T USUALLY
LET PETER
TALK ME INTO THIS
KIND OF STUFF.
WAIT A MINUTE.
BRIAN. YOU HAVE
A PRE-EXISTING
RELATIONSHIP WITH
THIS DEGENERATE?
A DEGENERATE.
AM I?
WELL. YOU ARE
A FASTIZIO.
SEE?
I CAN MAKE UP WORDS.
TOO. SISTER.
WELL. I THINK
WE FOUND
YOUR X-FACTOR.
WHAT? DO YOU
MEAN PETER?
HIS BEHAVIOR IS CLEARLY
A NEGATIVE INFLUENCE ON YOU.
AND WITH YOUR
INTELLIGENCE AND
SENSITIVITY. OBVIOUSLY...
WHOA. HEY!
I MADE MY OWN
MISTAKES. ALL RIGHT?
THIS MAN TOOK ME
INTO HIS HOME.
A-AND HE TREATED
ME LIKE FAMILY.
HE'S MY
BEST FRIEND.
YES. AND LOOK
WHERE YOU'VE
ENDED UP.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK MY THERAPY
HERE IS COMPLETE.
I CAME HERE
TO GET CLEAN.
AND I DID.
SO GOOD-BYE.
BRIAN. IT'S MOMENTS
LIKE THIS THAT
MAKE ME SAD
YOU'RE GONNA DIE 50
YEARS BEFORE I DO.
♪ HE WAS ALL COKED UP ♪
♪ AND WE WERE CHOKED UP ♪
♪ BUT NOW WE'RE HAPPY
BRIAN'S HOME.
CHA-CHA-CHA! ♪
I AM SERIOUS. LOIS.
YOU COULD BE
IN SHOW BUSINESS!
HEY. MEG.
18 YET?
NO.
HEY. CHRIS.
HOW ARE YOU?
WELL.
I'M GLAD I...
ALL RIGHT!
BRIAN. I FEEL
A LITTLE GUILTY.
IF IT WASN'T FOR ME.
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
EXPOSED TO THAT JUNK.
HEY. JOE. IF I'VE
LEARNED ANYTHING FROM
MY EXPERIENCE.
IT'S THAT WE'RE
ALL RESPONSIBLE
FOR OUR OWN DESTINY.
AND THAT'S WHY
I'M LEAVING.
LEAVING?
YOU CAN'T LEAVE.
I HAVE TO. PETER.
FOR ME.
I LOVE YOU ALL.
AW.
SOMEBODY
SAY SOMETHING.
BRIAN. WAIT!
H-HOLD ON
A SECOND.
AIRPORT. PLEASE.
♪